<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="eatery">Eateries</string>
    <string name="places">Places</string>
    <string name="malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="hospitals">Hospitals</string>

    <string name="lagos">Lagos</string>
    <string name="lagosLocation">City In Nigeria</string>
    <string name="overview"> Area: 1,171 km² \n Elevation: 41 m \n

Weather: 29°C \n Wind SW at 11 km/h \n 80% Humidity \n
Area code: 010
    </string>

    <string name="landOfLagos">Lagos, Land of Opportunities</string>

    <string name="lagosOne">
        Lagos, Nigeria’s largest city, sprawls inland from the Gulf of Guinea across Lagos Lagoon. Victoria Island,
        the financial center of the metropolis, is known for its beach resorts, boutiques and nightlife.
        To the north, Lagos Island is home to the National Museum Lagos, displaying cultural artifacts and craftworks.
        Nearby is Freedom Park, once a colonial-era prison and now a major venue for concerts and public events.
    </string>

    <string name="lagosTwo">
        Beaches line the Lekki Peninsula running east from the city, while inland, the Lekki
        Conservation Centre offers wildlife and trails. The National Gallery of Modern Art shares a building with the
        National Arts Theatre, and showcases works by Nigerian artists. Local arts and crafts can be found at colorful
        Lekki Market, and at private galleries across the city. North of the center, the life of Lagos musician Fela Kuti is
        celebrated at the Kalakuta Museum. To the west, the town of Badagry contains
        sites and museums documenting the town's history as a slave port, including the Badagry Heritage Museum
    </string>

    <string name="lagosThree">

    </string>

    <string name="visit">When To Visit</string>

    <string name="visitTwo">
        Many travelers arrive November–March, which is the warmest, driest part of the year, and is the best time to
        visit the beach. Rainy season is March–October, with precipitation peaking June–July. Popular events that draw crowds
        include Carnival (Easter); the Lagos Black Heritage Festival (Apr), with art exhibits and performances in dance,
        drama, and music; the Afrobeat music event Felabration (October),
        honoring the genre's founder; and the Eyo Festival (dates vary), featuring parades of masquerading dancers
    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello world</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating : </string>
    <string name="rating_number">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_name">Alhaja Mimiko</string>
    <string name="hotel_desc">I am so hay to be here honestly, and it means a lot to me.</string>
    <string name="rate">8</string>
</resources>
